Donor is in good condition
Hello
This radio wave... how...
The information is fine.
The donor committed suicide.
Oh, why do you do this at such a young age?
That is to say
Where's the surgeon?
I am coming
Hello
What is the status?
Need to be removed now
What is the situation
Is this a tattoo?
-tatoo? -tatoo
- I think I've seen it somewhere.
- I also think I've seen it somewhere.
I seem to have seen it in a history book.
Silent Recitation
I was someone's love and
someone's longing donor.
-=In Surgery=-
Spread love on this land today..
My Arm
How come this body is like a piece
of iron? It's really a waste of knife
It's not like he has super powers...
Scare me
What's wrong? What's
wrong? What are you doing?
- What's wrong? - Ghost
Is anyone there?
Doctor Come Out Don't come out
- Come out.
- Don't come out. Don't come out.
- Come out. - Don't come out.
Sprinkling
-=Lee Jae-in, Ahn Jae-hong=-
-=Yoo Ah-in Ra Mi-ran=-
-=Kim Hee-won Oh Jung-se=-
-=Shin Goo Park Jinyoung=-
-=Chen Xiqiong Zhang Guang=-
-=Unidentified=-
-=Special power possessed
by unknown tattoos=-
-=Superpower person??=-
-=#Superpowers#Heroes=-
-=[News Flash] A superpowered
person at the tire factory fire scene=-
It really doesn't hurt, right?
I've said it several times, it doesn't hurt
This is no way to defeat the original body.
I was supposed to vomit and drool.
Because a strange heart has
entered the body. This entry
Stand firm on your feet
You're abnormal.
Isn't it a good thing to not feel any pain?
Yes.
No pain is a good thing.
But it may not be a good thing, so I...
So please let me leave the hospital.
If it doesn't hurt, you'll have to act.
What's on your wrist? Do you have a tattoo?
No, I don't know if this is
a side effect of the surgery.
Did you make some bad friends?
Where do my friends come from?
Don't lose your temper and eat slowly
Look, my heart rate is over 90.
Besides
Don't buy this stuff
- You have no money again.
- Why does your father have no money?
If you want to make something
or eat something, just ask.
I have something I want to do
Even though
- I want to go back to Taekwondo. - No.
Didn't you let me just say it?
No, Taekwondo is definitely
not allowed. It's dangerous.
The doctor clearly said that
I could exercise moderately.
What do doctors know?
Only your father and I know
Why should I get a heart
transplant if I can't even exercise?
If you really want to exercise,
you can go to college and do Pilates.
- Dad. - Your dad.
My heart stops beating when I
think of you in the middle of a race
Sleeping can be scared to death
Your mother
Your mother also had a heart attack.
Your grandfather also
died of a heart attack.
If even my child is
like this, I, as a father,
It's better to just follow along.
Eternal Life and Eternal
Spring, the God of Sai is Coming
The Immortality of the
Soul Beyond the Restoration
Eternal Life and Eternal
Spring, the God of Sai is Coming
The Immortality of the
Soul Beyond the Restoration
Yes Spirit
That is to say
Organs are not batteries.
This is the first time
This time it's the pancreas
Anyway, fortunately, my father
should be able to leave this time.
Anyway
I'll hand it all over.
Don't bargain.
The Immortality of the
Soul Beyond the Restoration
Eternal Life and Eternal
Spring, the God of Sai is Coming
The Immortality of the
Soul Beyond the Restoration
Eternal Life and Eternal
Spring, the God of Sai is Coming
I'm so hungry.
Give me some grilled meat
Okay, be more moderate.
Reach out
- Dad. - No.
- I haven't said it yet.
- Taekwondo is definitely not an option
No, I'm not saying this.
Did you exercise in PE class? I
can see your heart rate is rising.
Knee Kick
- I didn't exercise.
- Then why did your heart rate increase?
What is
I really am. If you do this
again, I will throw this away.
I'm going to be a designated driver today
You go back first
Buy a new pair of shoes on the way back
If you have money, buy some
healthy food with your friends.
Okay, that's all for today.
I don't have any friends
Taekwondo, thank you for your hard work
You are late today, so I will punish you.
Kick 50 times
Taekwondo Big Brother
Why do I owe 100,000 won in monthly rent?
I was just about to explain it to you.
Oh, look at this kid.
Boy, are you kicking like that
to pick a fight or to make friends?
Sister, when I was your age
You can do a 540 turn now. Let's go.
I said this for your own good.
Keep your center of gravity
Stare at your target
Zhong Bi, you did this.
What happened?
Dad
A child who can become a
great man has come to our dojo
Ah Taekwondo
sorry
- Come on. - Got it.
-=Dad, you can't run away
just to meet your friends!!=-
-=Heartbeat exceeds __=-
Five Four
Greasy food is bad for the pancreas..
- Chunhua - Yes, my father
Thank you for your hard work
during this period of time.
- I'm sorry. - It's nothing.
You are healthy, believers can be blessed
You are alive so that
millions of people can...
People are really amazing
Even if I fall into a
coma with a ventilator
This ear can still hear clearly
When my father was still alive
I said all kinds of good and bad things.
Ouch
I can hear all of this, my God.
What I mean is
What the hell am I?
-=Director of Saishen
Hospital Song Haolin=-
If we use a car as an analogy
-=Director of Saishen
Hospital Song Haolin=-
From the engine to the parts
-=Director of Saishen
Hospital Song Haolin=-
From the engine to the parts
They all look like sports cars..
Is this possible just because
I received a pancreas donation?
Then I'll accept it once.
So I think
Anyway, this
Maybe the donor has a special physique.
How do donors
Do you have super powers?
-=Superpower=-
-=Superpowers witnessed the
scene (definitely not fake!!!)=-
I said I don't practice Taekwondo,
why do you always wear a uniform?
-=Barcelona Taekwondo=-
Because it is comfortable to wear
Did the doctor say that comfortable
clothing is good for the heart?
-=Barcelona Taekwondo=-
Did the doctor say that comfortable
clothing is good for the heart?
You can only wear it,
absolutely not practice Taekwondo
Don't run. Walk slowly.
Okay, I'll go slowly.
The uncle has been hanging around the
entrance of our gymnasium since just now.
Is he an exhibitionist,
a stalker, or a kidnapper?
All three are crimes
Arm Hello Arm
My Arm
arm
The heart is really strong.
I think I need to go to the doctor
to get a diagnosis certificate.
Such a big guy was gently grabbed
by a female junior high school student
Why does a female junior high
school student have such a tone?
Because my grandfather raised
me when I was learning to speak
You don't know the
extent of your ability yet.
I thought my growth
disk was opened too fast.
Who would have thought
this was a super power?
- Does your mother know?
- I don't have a mother.
Do you have a dad?
Dad has
If he knew this, he would probably
cry for three days and two nights.
Then he made a scene, so I
absolutely couldn't tell him
well done
Super powers are
supposed to be kept secret.
So what secret superpower do you have?
But who is the donor who has such ability?
Did you know that a person
can donate six organs?
Have no idea
Heart Lungs Cornea Kidneys Liver Pancreas
It means there are four other
people besides the two of us.
If we find the other four transplant
recipients, we'll probably have some clues.
How to find it?
-= "The 17th Share Hope Transplant Sports Meet" was held at
Shengwangli=- The 17th Sharing Life Transplant Sports Conference
Held today in Seoul
The National Transplant Sports
Conference is held every two years
Prospective transplant
recipients and their families
A total of about 100 people participated
Huang Zaiyuan, President
of the Transplant Association
Before the competition officially begins
Jump Jump
-=Golden Paradise Game Hall=-
-=The 17th Sharing Hope Transplant Games=-
Run well, this is the track
Nike
I just need shoes.
Have you looked carefully?
No No
Hey, take it away.
Look for it carefully.
Why do you look at your phone every day?
Uncle, you don't have any friends, right?
Why do we need friends?
Try this
No, this is a free tasting.
I'm very healthy after my kidney transplant
I give it to you because I am so grateful.
Good for the stomach
Thanks
What is there?
If you have a bad stomach
It contains prebiotics and probiotics
Can clean the stomach
-Vitamins and vegetables -Auntie
Look at your arms.
Arm?
The other arm
What happened to your arm?
- No apple flavor? - Yes.
But if you eat too much of
this, your stomach will hurt.
Ah, we still have food and salad.
Salads are 5% cheaper
if delivered regularly
Let me show you what's going on.
I ran fast after my heart transplant
Like this, my strength has also increased.
This man received a lung transplant.
Show it
-=Dried fish darts event. Hit the darts and get free
draft beer! Hit the target every time from 7pm to 10pm =-
What's going on?
Feed Dried fish
What is that?
Auntie, what are you capable of?
Me
No
Did you experience any
changes after the surgery?
Although I can't see
But everyone says my skin has improved.
Become beautiful
Oh, how am I beautiful?
Is it a superpower to become beautiful?
-Being beautiful is a superpower
nowadays -It's not to that extent
No
Recently many people pretend to buy Yakult
You always ask me for my number?
They all say they think of their first love
I said no.
Please use slowly
Auntie, don't you have a tattoo?
If you have a tattoo
It must be a superpower. It
seems you haven't discovered it yet.
This uncle is a superpower
who knows everything.
When people with special
abilities gather together
There will also be unknown abilities
You'll know when you find the rest.
How to find the rest
Park Wan-seo Heart Transplant
Chende Middle School Grade 3 Class 2
Taekwondo Primary School
Five consecutive championships
My future dream is to marry Do Kyung-soo
Is Do Kyungsoo a member of BTS?
It's EXO
Kim Sun-nyeo Kidney Transplant
If you were born in 1975, you
are a rabbit and you are unmarried.
First love is still written on her face
Park Ji-sung lung transplant
- Occupation - Stop talking
Who are you
I am Huang Qidong, the
one who started it all
I had a corneal transplant.
How did you find us?
Don't we all have a tattoo?
If this is within a few
kilometers radius, it will glow.
But since I'm the only one who
can see it, I can't explain it
So what the uncle did just now was
Control electromagnetic waves,
WIFI or something like that?
This
Here it comes
Another 500cc cup, please
good
It's amazing
You can be our superpower captain.
- Captain is shit - As
captain, find someone else
It's not a military regime.
Doesn't it mean that you have to
be within a few meters to see it?
Who knows where they are?
Then let's do the same
hacking attack as before.
- Hacking is bullshit. - Not in the movies.
Is it a dictatorship?
If you are caught spying on civilians
Will violate the Privacy Protection Act
and the Information and Communications Act
Personal information
leakage and reputation damage
It seems you don't know this.
Didn't you say you wanted to find it first?
I mean this method is unfair.
You think it's troublesome?
I'm too busy
You don't have a job?
- Who said that? - What do you do?
I'm a screenwriter. I write scripts.
What script to write
-Hero -Show me
Ends next week
You like heroic themes?
Then you know the community
in that circle, right?
We have a lot of hero information there.
- So you like us? - Yes
We are one of the people there. The
local distortion of facts is very serious.
You are a leftist.
I'm telling you, this is
the end of our conversation.
You're almost saying this in plain
language. What year were you born?
-88 -I am 87
- I was born in early 1988.
- What month exactly?
- How fast is April?
- Is April still considered the beginning of the year?
- Isn't this a national regulation?
- What's the basis for it not being a national regulation?
What is the basis for the basis?
Hey, what are you doing?
It's such a nice day.
Reborn from a body
Live like a family.
Uncle, didn't we agree to split the bill?
Oh, it's really not quiet
What show will you show me this time?
Do I want these poor souls to work for me?
If you complain about the high price now
I'll go find someone else.
You know that the Republic of
Korea is full of evil, right?
So many tricks
All out
Eternal Life and Eternal
Spring, the God of Sai is Coming
Omniscience and Blessings God Returns
Congratulations on your
resurrection, Lord Saishen
You, a busy man, are here.
Because I want to save one more poor soul.
We must learn from Sai Shen.
Why does it sound to me like
you're trying to steal my opportunity?
Did you get an ear
injury when you were a kid?
You heard wrong
No No
I can hear clearly.
How much money does my daughter want?
If we hand over the consortium,
But she didn't want to hand
over the pharmaceutical company.
Because this is the
business her father founded.
A filial daughter, your daughter
Bingchun
Our family has no filial sons or
daughters from generation to generation.
Blood is greedy
Originally, each follower counted as 45.
Then I'll give you 50
If you give me the Renaissance
Isn't it because of you
that my ears are injured?
When performing stunts at Zhengshan Market
- You dialed the wrong number.
- 550,000 won
So I beat you like a dog
It's on my pants.
- We sold a lot of drugs that day.
- Don't say it, brother.
The drug dealer's henchman,
the guy who shits in his pants
You really think you're a god.
Damn it, stop talking, you drug dealer
Stop talking about poop. Damn it.
You guy
There are 5 minutes left at noon.
You have to be back to
your position 5 minutes ago
To do exactly what you should do
-=Sai Shen Consortium=-
Accurate time will keep us safe
Please wear a helmet
-=Sai Shen Consortium=-
Three minutes left
Users cannot force time to work
Don't you know this is a
violation of the Labor Standards Act?
You know so much about the
law, why don't you become a judge?
Why do this here?
Please do not treat us differently
because we are contract employees.
It's not the contractors'
problem, even the president
If the rest time is observed
That's the law I know.
The one who doesn't
comply is this consortium.
In order to catch up with the date
of the revival meeting or something
Working overtime every day and
not having enough safety equipment
If something happens, will you save us?
That leader will save
In the hell college, the guy
who didn't even get redemption
How dare you mention the god of race?
- What happened to him?
- He fell from above
No, I've said it many times.
Let you change that, really
Answer the phone?
When will someone come?
-=You who put safety
first are superheroes=-
I saw
Why don't you believe what people say?
It's not that I don't believe
This is called cataract in medical terms.
- Of course, dopamine is secreted when you are excited.
- No, no
I'm not excited. I can see it clearly.
Why do we have to eat meat
that we rarely eat before?
Huang Shenling suddenly grew white hair
That tree too
- At that time,
Do people who donate organs
have special physical conditions?
It may also be a special physique
People who receive organ transplants
There should be more.
One more time
Where does the pollen come from?
That's it.
Go ahead. It's already started.
Don't you go out to play on weekends?
No friends?
I have no friends
Why
Because of dad?
No, although there is also this reason
But I took a year off due to
illness, so I don't have any friends
I understand
When I was sick, I didn't
When I am not sick, I am afraid of
getting sick, so I have no friends.
People with super powers are lonely.
Do you know that?
Have no idea
Do you know what it is?
What is
Bad Guy
Among the same kind of superpowers
And will attack other superpowered people
Why
Do you want to have all the
super powers for yourself?
That's why we have to
find the bad guys first.
Before the power is taken away
We
To us
People with super powers are meant to
be friends with people with super powers.
Don’t rich people hang
out with rich people?
Uncle You try this
Why Give it a try
Uncle
If you get caught by a
bad guy, just tell me.
I will rescue all the people in our team.
Wanshu
But
How do you spot the bad guys?
Just look and you will know
You can tell at a glance
This guy is a bad guy
Just take care of yourself
Eat two chicken wings at a time
Wanshu
Zhixing
Oh my god, I found it. I found it.
I found out what my super power is.
Take a look
Look at it.
Boom boom boom boom
I don't have super powers, do I?
Why only my tattoo?
Round like a knockoff owl
Auntie, why do you want super powers?
If you have super powers
It can save lives, right?
Like a hero
Having super powers doesn't
necessarily make you a hero.
Why
Experience
Positivity
Number of people saved
Degree of self-sacrifice
These are all scored.
Not everyone can be a hero
I don't really like the score line style.
Hey, is he coming or not?
Can he find it with his
amazing hacking skills?
Have no idea
Ask again when you come.
If you eat too much, you
will have a stomachache
You said you would
come, but you came so late
Young
You can also send a message
-=OK=-
-=Park Ji-sung: Okay, let's do this=-
-=Huang Qidong, save me=-
I will return the money to you
Is money an issue, you son of a bitch?
How can you win 11
jackpots in one location?
Eleven times
This machine seems to be
broken. What do you want to do?
Take off your glasses
No, this doesn't seem to be bad.
I will compensate
Nonsense
I see you hit the jackpot with
just a flick of your finger, right?
Are you Pikachu?
Will it create static electricity?
No, I'm not Pikachu.
It's a superpower
Wow you are so funny
I have to call your brother Long Jiu
Let me send a text message first.
That one needs to be pushed.
I've already said that if you eat
too much, you'll get a stomachache.
I ate five more
Where did you go?
Junior high school students
are not allowed to enter here
This is not an internet cafe
I was supposed to be in high school.
But I took a year off.
No matter if you are a high school student
or something, this is not an Internet cafe
Auntie, I don't drink Yakult
stomachache
I'm not here to sell Yakult
I'm here to take him away.
I've said he's not someone
you can just take away.
This guy caused a scene in the store.
I'm in debt and I've turned off my
phone. What do you think I should do?
Hello
No more paper
there
Hanging
Is it your friend?
No
Uncle
Let him go.
My dad is a Taekwondo master
My dad is a convict with
four prior convictions.
You didn't hear me just now, did you?
This uncle made a mess in the store.
So this uncle suffered a heavy loss.
The person who caused the accident
shall bear the compensation for the loss
Not a friend
He has no friends
He needs to be taught a lesson.
It's really useless
no
We're going to eat ribs.
Wait till you finish your lesson.
I feel like I've been reborn.
Otherwise, leave
I walk my own Yangguan Road
Don't do this
Just let him go
Ah, what?
This is a gift for you.
You guys
You really ignored my words.
They say I have a bad stomach.
Beef ribs or pork ribs
I've been in there for ten minutes.
Are all four of you here?
It took exactly 4 minutes and 28 seconds
Go fast
Call your dad.
Just called
What is that?
Exceed the past
That guy
what to do
Power 5
Get out of the way
what to do
kick off
This won't work. Stop it.
I've said it before.
It's my brother who sees you as pitiful.
Take off your glasses, bastard.
So dirty
Stop
Four people
We are full.
This buffet is quite delicious.
Because someone has suffered so much
In the end, they didn't
even settle the bill.
If you don't know, you might
think it was you who paid the bill.
Are you speaking plain language?
This is like a honorific, right?
Stop arguing, we are all
friends with super powers
Friend is a ghost
Do you still want to keep him with you?
If you have the ability, then
hack in and find it yourself.
Is it because I can't
do it that I don't do it?
It's because it's against the law.
Then you who abide by the law
Why would you plagiarize
someone else's script?
Did you doxx me?
Yes
Talking about justice all day long
So I looked at
What screenwriter
A script that was sold
with great difficulty
Stealing from friends?
That's why I have no friends.
This guy is a well-known
malicious commenter.
How many times have you been sued?
I'm not the kind of guy who gives bad
reviews without even watching a movie.
This is a beggar boy.
Did you know that your coin
has now dropped to a quarter?
Only 80,000 yuan left
-=One throw=-
You have to earn money honestly.
A mother who works as a nanny
for others and earns money for you
Don't you feel pity for her?
I would have committed suicide long ago.
How can you talk like that?
Some things can be said,
some things cannot be said
He actually said suicide
Let's go
Brother Jixing, please be patient
What are you enduring?
Really, why are you like this?
Didn't we agree to be friends?
I just want to play with you
because I feel sorry for you.
You really thought you were friends.
Come here
What are you guys doing?
In this case, let's not meet for now.
Why didn't you answer the
phone? Where have you been?
How did it become like this again?
Who are you with?
Are you with friends?
I have no friends
What are you doing alone so late?
Who is your friend? Give me your number.
I've said I don't have any friends.
I thought you were in trouble and ran
to the police station and the hospital.
Even the morgue
I even searched the morgue.
I'm not feeling well now.
Is it time to play with friends?
Really, I have no friends.
I said I have no friends
None
Everybody hates me
I'm a useless person
Since everyone hates me so much
I might as well have died.
Why are you dying?
I'm suffocating because of my dad.
It's not because my heart hurts.
It's because Daddy is
about to stop beating.
Am I a dog?
Why did you put a dog collar on me?
I'm really suffocating because of my dad.
I don't need a dad at all
Wanshu
Don't run, you'll slip.
Have a cup of tea before you go.
Don't bring anything here anymore.
Sorry
I heard you had a heart transplant.
Looks like a success.
Looks much better.
Look, your skin has improved.
Madam, you look very young.
After all, I took someone else's life.
Of course you have to get better.
Isn't it?
I was wrong
The rest of life
I will do good things
for the rest of my life.
Do what your husband couldn't finish.
Save many people
I hope you don't go on living.
It's better to commit suicide again.
I hope you don't fail
this time and succeed.
Stop saying you're going to die.
Let someone like my husband die.
I hope you die
Let's do it
What
Study this to develop new drugs
- What are you talking about?
- Dean Song retired
Three more years?
Three years and four months
After retirement
Going to change the grandchildren's diapers
Or be the vice president
of a pharmaceutical company?
What
my country
It's time for a Nobel Prize in Medicine
So what to do
Feel like you can do it
Why are you here?
Have you really missed everyone?
Didn't auntie say goodbye?
Didn't you say you were
looking for bad guys?
I have found the bad guy.
Don't look for him anymore.
This, this uncle is not a bad guy, just...
A bit like a minion
Not that guy. I mean I'm the bad guy.
You were sick too, you know.
If you feel uncomfortable physically,
you will also feel uncomfortable mentally.
Then I don't want to
see those powerful people
I don't want to see myself hiding
behind those people and cursing at them.
It is a formula for people who have accomplished
nothing and have nothing to be bad people.
But you have super powers.
What can this do?
If I had super powers, like that guy
It would be great if it
was a useful superpower.
What kind of superpower is this?
It's obviously not a superpower.
Are you sure you want this?
That's how I am, that's
why I live like this
I didn't plagiarize the script.
We were supposed to write together
He left and said he wanted
to write something else.
Uncle
Are you really playing with me
because you feel sorry for me?
This sentence cancels
Say sorry to Aunt Shannv.
Go there and tell it yourself.
Where to go
They said they found a
liver transplant candidate.
Monitor
Now these people are not our followers.
If we improve safety and treatment, etc.
Then it won't be finished
before the Day of Resurrection.
I climbed 50 or 60 floors without a rope.
Safety first, as stated by Shinshin
So where is the place blessed by the new
god? Where is the need for safety equipment?
It's all because of no trust
I became scared.
Let’s go eat Regional Director
Fifteen minutes until lunch time
Let’s do it after dinner.
We are not robots.
- How can this be completed in one day?
- It's a robot.
Let's go eat.
I want to finish this today.
Someone must faint.
Good
When you come back, bring
me a bucket of instant noodles
knew
good
He won't come. He doesn't
want to come at all.
What to do when you come?
You must give me oxygen.
I've been arguing all
day over useless abilities.
Excuse me
I'm leaving first
You go see it.
Why
Don't you want to find super powers?
I'm sorry, Wanshu.
Not eligible
How can you say that?
Didn't we agree to find super
powers together and become heroes?
Start up
You've seen me too, right?
I'm not qualified.
I didn't... I didn't look that closely.
Such a precious ability
should be used in a good place
I'm sorry for causing trouble
to you all during this period.
I won't do it anymore
Really annoying
In a world where it’s hard to feed yourself
What kind of superhero is it?
Why do you want to help others?
Disbanded today.
The group chat was also disbanded
Nothing happened
Don't be nervous.
What are you doing?
Didn't you hear the sound?
- Get out quickly.
- You just said it was nothing.
The regional director
asked us to stay on the job.
If you die, will the
district chief be responsible?
Get out now
Two lines two lines
Slow down. Slow down.
Where did this come from?
Have you found the right path?
I don't know either
Lee Soo-geun
I'm here, monitor.
But we were here before, right?
Help!
Lee Soo-geun
Wear a hard hat
Uncle, get out of the way
Auntie, no
There's someone inside
Start Open Door
Wait a moment
Start Quickly
Should I open the door?
Open
Sorry for last time.
Are there any swimming goggles
or anything like that here?
The smoke is so thick I can't see anything.
Turn off the song.
Start up
good
Found it
I'll tell you, go in.
Who are you to command me?
I told you I would be your guide.
If there is navigation, then you go in.
Are you two crazy? How can you quarrel now?
No, I opened the door for you.
Ask me to tell you the
way, and I will tell you.
What else do I need to do for you?
I'm not asking you to do anything else.
I asked you not to command me.
You command me so I won't command you
Why do you give me instructions?
I didn't tell you what to do.
I asked you not to command me.
- You told me not to boss
you around - Damn you two
As soon as they see each other,
they start to quarrel and go crazy
You two are stupid.
Don't let me in.
Uncle, tell us the way
left
A little further
Not there
Yes, that's it.
Going forward
Shougen
Here, here...
Lee Soo-geun
Hey, Shougen, wake up!
Uncle
Water... water?
Hurry and get some water
Water Water...
what to do
- Water - What to do? What to do?
Don't just stand there,
at least do something.
Auntie, what's going on?
Stop
Where to start
Not where I am
You asked me to get some water and
asked me where it was. How would I know?
What about superheroes?
Uncle, please go out first.
I know where the water purifier is.
Come with me
Send him outside
Please
Shougen
This way
Just walk another hundred meters.
There's no gas mask at
this construction site?
Sorry
I just saw a lot of tanks here
Is there such a thing as an oxygen tank?
Here comes the oxygen tank
Not over there
My name is Xu Yaoshan
Had a liver transplant
Occasionally treat existing
underlying medical conditions
Fractures and injuries
caused by accidents alone
Shoulder discomfort, chronic fatigue, etc.
I can cure them all.
If you need anything, tell me.
Are you also a designated driver?
-My dad does it, too. -Just now I saw you
You seem to be transferring
other people's pain away
It's okay. I just need a glass of water.
It will be fine
real
People like you are truly heroes.
Isn't it?
Applaud
applaud
Miss What
I think you are a real hero
And saved my life
Thank you very much
What what
What are you looking at?
Ah, Auntie, don't cry.
You were cursing just now. Why are you
crying now? This doesn't suit you at all.
This is even more terrifying
Actually, I used to have depression
and anger regulation disorder.
I have to take medicine vigorously
Then after the operation,
the patient became healthy.
Do you think things have
really gotten better now?
- I thought swearing was your superpower.
- Ouch
Forget about what happened just now
Should we give each of our heroes a name?
What's the name again?
No, don't you see those
foreign superhero movies?
What kind of hero, what kind of woman
As for me, I rely on my
strength to save people.
How about saving women? The
abbreviation is saving women.
Do you think it's OK?
The English word is "NINE" ("救"
is pronounced the same as "九").
NINE GIRL
- Uh... - Uncle, you are an oxygen tank
Jar Jar Boy Bar Jar Jar Boy
What's your name, Auntie?
I was originally doing fresh delivery and
was thinking of calling myself 'Fresh Girl'
Is that a bit like that?
But fresh girl is more
catchy than fresh woman, right?
Just call it that.
As long as we don't call you.
- Your name is Yaoshan. - Yes
Let's call it medicine hand.
The hand is medicine hand.
You, because your name is Startup
- Bluetooth Man, the wireless one.
- Oh, ok, ok.
Hey, save the girl
- You are a bad student, right?
- My dad said that he just wants me to be healthy.
I actually have a name in mind.
I can save people and replenish my energy.
Battery Man
- Everyone uses English names, so it can be unified.
- Yeah, OK. Battery
Okay, we've come up with a name
and the atmosphere is pretty good.
Bluetooth Man, in line with
today's atmosphere, music follows you
Super amazing
But uncle, this is
really amazing, look at it
Action
again
Enough
-=Barcelona Taekwondo=-
Where did you go?
Go meet friends
Didn't you say you have no friends?
I made friends
- Do you need my help?
- You don't have the strength
You will get hurt. Get out of the way.
See?
Dad is still okay, right?
- It's OK. - Since it's OK
Leave everything to Dad, okay?
- Dad. - Where's Dad?
Even if you become an old
lady, as long as you call me dad
I will also appear like a hero
and help you solve all the problems.
Colds are bad for your health
I have to go to the hospital tomorrow.
You should go back to bed early.
Sai Shen Hospital prays
for a speedy recovery
Always focus...
Sorry, please take the next elevator
Feel sorry
What you may experience during treatment...
Come up, fellow believers.
Which department?
The Eternal Life Wing Chun Sai God Descends
I am Xu Yaoshan, the stage equipment
construction team leader of Saishen Group.
It's a pleasure to meet you
Were you scared by the
explosion a while ago?
- Are you hurt? - I'm fine.
Thank you for your concern
Thank you for your faith.
Yes
I will try harder to believe
The Eternal Life Wing Chun Sai God Descends
You got a tattoo?
This is not a tattoo. I was lucky
enough to have an organ transplant.
What was transplanted
Underwent liver transplantation
Did anything change after the transplant?
The surgery went well and my body became healthy and I don't feel tired anymore...
- I'm not talking about that.
Is it that you have any special place?
Although I'm not sure
But people say I look younger.
Of course, you need to rely
on your liver to become younger
What's your name?
My name is Xu Yaoshan
Xu Yaoshan, Construction Team Leader
Take good care of your body
See you next time
-=A book to help you
learn how to be a nurse=-
Looks like she's preparing
for the nursing exam.
-=A book to help you
learn how to be a nurse=-
No, just watching for fun
-=A book to help you
learn how to be a nurse=-
Wow, so cool
-=A book to help you
learn how to be a nurse=-
Wow, so cool
I'm so sorry, driver.
Suddenly said we want to meet here
Do you need me to turn around?
Ouch. I'm so sorry.
Let me see where the Saishen
Pharmaceutical Headquarters is.
Oh, Saishen Pharmaceuticals?
I work next door.
I know the way
Very good
- Please get through safely. - Okay.
- Do you have any gum?
Why not start
Yeah
This first requires a
pathological examination
Even a lethal dose of
anesthesia would not work
Is it Little Sai Shen?
Great! I am Xu Yaoshan, the
construction team leader of Saishen Group.
Little Sai Shen, where is
this? I... want to go home.
Oh, by the way, there is a book that will
teach you how to be a nurse. I forgot that.
- We have to go there...
- What's the anesthesia?
Directly
Little Sai Shen
Shut up
Since anesthesia doesn't work, we
have to find a way to make him pass out.
What are you standing there
for? Why don't you start?
-Yes. -Who are you waiting for?
Are you waiting for me?
The Eternal Life Wing Chun Sai God Descends
You have planned
something very interesting.
See you again, Xu Yaoshan, construction
team leader, it's okay, it's okay
Who did it?
Dean Song is a Saishen
I heard that if you take just a little
bit of the liver it will grow back.
- Right? - Yes, that's right.
The Eternal Life Wing Chun Sai God Descends
Become a sleeping sacrifice
and live forever in my body
Doctor Kim tied up
sorry
It seems that the same kind cannot
Then let's do surgery.
- Mr. Zhao - Yes, President
It's better to strike first.
Catch them all
Take it easy. Ouch. Take it easy.
Auntie, this way
Okay, here we come
Oh, thank you.
- Is there anything to drink?
- Yes, yes, yes. How could there be nothing?
Daughter, daughter,
daughter, what are you doing?
What are you doing? Is
your leg okay? It's okay...
Hey, this is simple.
Hey, isn't it just a child?
Who are you?
- Let's go. - Where are we going?
Very soon
Daughter, go over there, far away
Go to the very edge
Ahhh my waist my waist I
almost thought I was going to die
Pause Pause Pause
Go up again
come on
All together up
Ah damn
Hey, do you know 540 degree rotation?
Oh mom
Xinqi finished eating a long time
ago. I'll give you the empty bucket now.
Didn't I tell you to call
dad if you have any problem?
Get me some water
- Water. - There's something in that bag.
-=Free gift event: All customers who purchase more than
50,000 won will receive a free Bluetooth speaker =-
I just said it
You got the wrong guy, sir.
-=Photoelectric Fire Detector=-
Let me out first.
Please let me go
Did my father promise to give you a job?
I don't need an official
position. What I want is very simple.
A few Nobel Prizes are enough
You're on the wrong side
It's no use for an old
man to become younger.
Who do you think will live longer?
Go check it out.
Who are you
Why did you come just now? I've
been waiting for you for a long time.
Who are you, bastard?
Have you been drinking in broad daylight?
Why don't you recognize me, your father?
Did I tell you
Your father was a handsome
man when he was young.
Plz follow me
This way, follow me.
- This preacher - Be
careful on the steps, go up
Follow this way too
Newcomers, please follow me here.
- This is it. - Welcome.
Where is my clone?
Have no idea
There must be someone left
before I can become a god.
Aren't you afraid?
If God really exists, aren't you
afraid that you will be punished?
Have you been to church recently?
Dad
Because I know I won't be forgiven
That’s why I want to be God.
How clever! Hiding it here!
Director Zhao, long time no see.
Who are you
Why are you playing
dumb? You clearly know it.
I have no idea
Don't be too harsh. The president
asked us to invite him formally.
Numbness Numbness
-=Really? Where are you?;;;;=-
What's going on?
Did you open the door?
Didn't we come here together?
Why don't you untie this? Untie it for me.
Hello Park Joo-chan Park Joo-chan
This bastard
Auntie Auntie
Don't mess with me Don't mess with me
-=Huang Qidong, save me!!=-
-=Huang Qidong, save me!!
We are all kidnapped!=-
-=Uncle, where are you?
Send me your address now=-
The eyes are definitely not allowed
My eyes are really not good.
Absolutely not my eyes, if you want
to take it, take my reproductive organs
He's really good at pretending to be sick.
Corneal transplant should be done soon.
Yes
Eyes not working
How nice it would be if the
rest of us did it together
- I'm still missing one person.
- I'm a rich man.
- I can give you a lot of money
- Just to be on the safe side
- It's better to have more time.
- I'll give you a lot of money.
How much is enough, you bastards?
Can you give him anesthesia?
Xu Yaoshan was so noisy
that he even fell into a coma
But it must be painful.
No what
Nothing works I have to go
No, no, absolutely not this time. You...
Do you think I don't
know what you're doing?
Since when did you know
Parents smell their children's farts
You can all tell what's on this kid's mind.
You've been in the hospital for three
years and you haven't made any friends.
After I got better, I
finally made some friends.
The same is true of the friends you make.
Hanging out with bad boys
Even if I buy you new shoes every time
When I came back, my shoes were
all broken and became garbage.
My daughter, I'm sorry, my daughter
So I study Taekwondo hard.
All for the sake of not getting beaten.
Because bad boys bullied you
- That's why you want to protect yourself.
- Dad
-But what if I get hurt again? -Actually
My friends were caught by the bad boys
Don't go. Don't go. Don't go.
We are like a family
So I have to rescue them.
Really not
You're standing right
behind me, you bastards
It's the group of people
in black suits, right?
Age is just a number
Do you want to change the song?
I still get excited when I hear this song.
I also listened to this song
when I went on stage in Barcelona
I won the championship
What's your dad's nickname?
-Taekwondo Injustice -Taekwondo Injustice
A fatal spinning kick full of justice
What's wrong
What's wrong? Wake up.
Why are you here? Where is this place?
It seems we have been kidnapped.
Let's go out first.
Where is the toilet?
No, not there.
No
How are you
This is so interesting. It's amazing.
You have never seen WIFI
with your naked eyes, right?
Is it because only one eye was removed?
Focus is good and bad
I'm sorry, it's all his fault for
waking up suddenly and rushing over
His cornea was transplanted
into only one of my eyes.
It makes me feel uncomfortable.
He must have seen this.
Can you still do this kind of thing?
Severe damage during removal
Modern medicine cannot restore
Who?
It's me
Battery Man
Uncle, please help me heal
Can't you treat it?
The battery is dead
Can't you recover by drinking water?
Drink some water and help me heal.
Didn’t I bring you water last time?
Uncle, help me, I'm so scared
How did he survive?
They were able to remove
my two organs twice.
-=Sai God Descends Great Revival=-
Eternal Life and Eternal
Spring, the God of Sai is Coming
Welcome to all the saints
and new believers here
Now, as he said, according
to the Lord's promise
Returned with a new body that never dies
Save us from the fire of hell
To punish the unbelievers,
He descended into us.
Welcome to the King of Kings, God of Gods
Our Xu Yongchun is a god
- Raise it. - Let's all call him together.
Saishen
What's going on?
Who is this
The Eternal Life Wing Chun Sai God Descends
Eternal immortality
beyond the physical body
I promised that when we meet again
I will stand before
you in my youthful body.
Those who believe in me and follow me
Will be my people
Eternal Life and Eternal
Spring, the God of Sai is Coming
Indestructible by fire, body of steel
I smashed the boulder
we promised on that day
Focus on you
Those who believe in me and follow me
Will be my people
Wait a moment
Doser
Sai Shen
Eternal Life Wing Chun Sai Shen Descends
All diseases will be eliminated
and the dead will be resurrected
Healing patients
Resurrection of the Dead
Thank you, Master
People who believe in me
My people
Sai Theism
Why are there so many entrances?
Are there any artists coming?
Scare me
I was scared to death
I told you not to run.
Eternal Life Wing Chun Sai Shen Descends
I will return after I
have fully become a god.
Please give your best praise
You are Wanshu
Brother, who are you?
She's really good looking.
Park Jong-min Ouch
Barcelona hero
I got into a lot of
fights when I was a kid.
Nice to meet you
Damn
It hurts, okay?
How do you educate your children?
- I'm sorry...
But you're talking to me like this now?
You are a bad boy.
Always say you, you, your to adults
You bastard, don't you
have a father at home?
Of course not at home.
My father was born in 1905
Brother, did you capture my friends?
My daughter actually did it.
- My daughter?
- She has been correcting herself recently.
Anyway, a little bit of that
alright
Okay, now that everyone has introduced their family
situations, it's time to get down to business.
Wanshu
Let me use your heart.
Is this guy crazy?
Hey, you guy
NINE GIRL
- Are you okay? - Yeah
I was planning to pick you up.
- You're just in time. But how did you get here?
- Ouch.
This should be your father, right?
- Hello. - Taekwondo. Taekwondo.
It's the final farewell.
- I have to say hello.
I am a fresh girl
This is the Jar Man
- Stop it. - Hey
- You are so lucky to have such an amazing daughter.
- Yes.
You must be at ease.
No, this child is still young and
weak. I am very worried about her.
What about you, Jar Girl?
Do you have any children?
I am a fresh girl
Cans... good
Kim Sunnyeo, let me say something too
Who are you
I am the Eternal Life,
Wing Chun, Sai Shen, Coming
Uncle
I think that brother is a
bad guy because he has tattoos
But why is that person the
elder brother and I am the uncle?
He is handsome.
Uncle, you are the type who needs care.
The adults are talking. Do you
want to keep interrupting them rudely?
That
Where is the startup and Mr. Xu Yaoshan?
Eaten by me
- Brat. - Don't.
Wait a moment
Hello Hello Hello
Not dead?
What to do
I...
Hey, hurry up, he's coming. He's coming.
Park Ji-sung
Lung transplantation
Oh, your profession...
Drool Launch
He shouldn't be dead.
But what did you just say?
Usually you have to show your special
moves before you use them. This is polite.
The saliva is so dirty
that I can't stand it
What did you just say you were doing?
What he is saying
Oh my god
What?
Wait a moment
emission
Let me see
Our Kim Sunnyeo is here
There is a way.
If our Kim Sunnyeo stood by me, we wouldn't
have to go through so much trouble.
Help me once.
It's a piece of cake to
transfer their abilities to me.
Don't come over here. Go away.
Transfer it to me. If you run out of
ability, I will help you fill it up.
No need to bleed. How neat!
Otherwise
Should I buy you a Yakult company?
Give me back my eyeballs
Song Haolin is really annoying
Eternal Life Wing Chun Sai Shen Descends
Become a true sacrifice
and live forever in my body
Why are you doing this?
I have two unfulfilled wishes in my life.
One is youth
What's the other one? You have to ask
me for the lines before you can take it.
- The other one is Yong...
- You will definitely say it is God, you don't even need to look at it
The need for a visible God
I became a god to save
mankind. You must be saying this.
I think you've been to a cult school.
Writing lines like this these
days will get you low marks.
You really ruin people's mood.
This guy is a famous
troll in the neighborhood.
Father Sai
Yes, Xu Yaoshan
Is everything fake?
Is everything you show fake?
I abandoned my brothers and family
All-night driving for your property
Dedicated to your life
Were we all deceived? Was it all in vain?
Um
So if you really want to see God
Just give me your lowly bodies.
Give me back my eyes, you bastard.
Go away Go away
What are you doing here?
Mother
Scare me
You should dye your hair.
Don't do it
Give him all our wealth.
Oh my god, what should I do?
What's going on?
-=Do not approach, please
watch with your eyes=-
New God Father New God Father
This can't be done
What?
If we open them all at
this time, we will all die.
Wait a minute, stop it, get out of the way
Let me breathe
Are you going to kill everyone up there?
Are you going to kill everyone
who believes in you and follows you?
The believers just need to be reunited
My image is the god of death
This is caused by you
-=Barcelona Taekwondo=-
Eternal Life New God
Will become a part of
me, an eternal existence
Jin Shannyu, give it to me now
Otherwise you will all die.
Wake up and open your eyes
Wake up, Jiang Wanshu, hello
Go to hell, asshole.
Brat
Go over there. Don't come over here.
-NINE GIRL -Hey Wanshu
We will witness the coming of the new god
Pray now
Uncle, how do I turn that off?
I don't know either
How could you not know
You have to use something like an
intradermal needle to disperse it.
But I'm not a technician
sorry
Give me the tattoos
What are you going to do?
I don't know. I have to try.
Hey, if you succeed, admit
that you are the same age as me
If you succeed, I'll be your brother.
What are you doing?
- What? - The power is out.
It's all done, just give me back my tattoo
I am your brother
Hey, stop tying me up, hold my hand
- Wait a minute. - Give it to me first.
Caught
Why do you want to win me?
People like you have to take
it out when I tell you to.
If you are told to die, you must die.
Enough is enough
NINE GIRL Let go, let go
Can't let go
dad
My child
How come it's so dirty?
Did you fall down? Did anyone hit you?
Who hit my weak daughter?
Daddy is sorry for not
coming here earlier. I'm sorry.
Is my daughter okay? It's Dad
who's sorry for you. I'm sorry.
Ouch, Dad, I'm sorry.
A brat
Medicine
Do you want to be a leader?
I want to be a nurse
Damn
It hurts
Oh, I'm going to drive. Wait
a minute. I'm going to drive.
Ouch
what to do
Ah, what should I do? The lactic
acid bacteria must have gone bad.
I want to deliver it at night.
I also ordered a lot of Vietnamese
spring rolls to lose weight
The parking lot is this way.
Blues Man
Bluetooth male
That is to say
We don't have anything to do.
Listen to a song while you wait
Which song to play?
Never mind. I'll let it go.
Play that song
Don't want to hear that
Do you know what it is?
That's right
Battery Man Um
Could you help me with this for a while?
As soon as I see a convenience store, I
will drink some water to help you heal.
No car keys.
That one is here.
Let's come up with a name
before the car arrives.
Didn't we give it a name last time?
We have a fake name but no group name.
When watching a foreign movie, Super
Power Assemble, I would first name it
Sister, please get up.
Is it English or Korean?
Sister, you decide.
I'm actually good at naming.
No, I'll name it.
Battery man, you've worked
hard. Please charge your battery.
I always feel that it would be
better to have a friendly feeling
Just like saying hello
Now I just thought of a suitable name
Yeah, there are five of us.
- Five people greet each other in English.
- Yes
I know that
I know what it is
Uncle, please do this
ah
-=Hi-FIVE=-